{
    "id": "47c00620ed924236bb064ab7772d7338",
    "title": "Quantifiers Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ".................................... people supported the project.",
            "description": "We use some before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "27e03141f28b492297597e1b2e94f9c1"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................  my friends are vegetarians.",
            "description": "We use some of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bd2bca8188e94b4aae5b0935d1dd18e0"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... them came forward to help me.",
            "description": "We use none of before a personal pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "None",
                "None of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af1af91f691e45d9bd4038beb7ba9a00"
        },
        {
            "question": "I spoke to ................................ the eye witnesses.",
            "description": "We use some of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ff5ee4ecb034883bf74dfb4fda4d1c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Take ................................... the shirts.",
            "description": "We use any of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "any of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06f00e05fc924e6b8c103c916c4d1c1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ the books in the library are missing.",
            "description": "We use some of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "810d6a08ea8545dba8e432234f168bf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... the keys open the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "None",
                "None of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0d21987ee4e42dea826ff8a09c93795"
        },
        {
            "question": "I spent ..................................... days with them last month.",
            "description": "Write a few to refer to a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fcd5116021b84e0494339e72587aa320"
        },
        {
            "question": "I drank ..................................... the milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc06782f62394a72949f64dea55b94b6"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... us enjoyed the party, but I was bored.",
            "description": "We use some of before a personal pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "02a0588455094436897ba2eff3d35895"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited ...................................... my friends.",
            "description": "All and all of can both be used before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "all of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1fbf83ca4d8e4896924a69f43ab65cb9"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................................... you have passed the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Both of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "40add95e4b794c209d1e2dfeca7ec09b"
        }
    ]
}